□+1 (765) 701-5596 | **S** sgchi@purdue.edu | **A** https://jisk984.github.io | **D** jisk984 | 🖻 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 🎓 Seunggeun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in Machine Learning and its applications to real-world problems. Representation Learning in Computer Vision problems is my primary study. My research also spans over Combinatorial Optimization problems which aim to extract rules by applying Reinforcement Learning.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor: ByungRo Moon

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019 B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING • Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

Publications

Conference Proceedings

• M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee. Learning to Escape to Promised Lands: Multi-mode Policy Learning for the Traveling Salesmen Problem. IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (TNNLS), 2022, submitted

- [C2] H, Chi, M, H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, O. Huang, K, Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021

Research & Project

HandVAE: An interactive 3D hand generation system

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Sept. 2021 - Apr. 2022

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- Targeting UIST 2022
- · Disentangled properties of hands with Beta-VAE
- Developed UI for interactive hand generation and annotation
- Developed federated learning system

Weakly Supervised Action Segmentation for Video

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

July. 2020 - Sept. 2020

· Introduced a loss function for video segmentation combining Triplet loss and Temporal Cycle Consistency Loss

- Defined the Action Segmentation problem as a Neural Machine Translation problem
- Visualized the attention matrices to interpret Machine's inference

Improving Multi-Joint dynamics with Contact(MuJoCo) by applying Hierarchical **Reinforcement Learning**

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

· Proposed a hierarchical architecture to give the agent frequent reward signals by setting subgoals

- Designed and developed a hierarchical architecture of model and environment • Applied policy gradient with self-critical sequence training in optimization

Predicting stock price by applying Combinatorial Optimization

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Analyzed data with the ANOVA(Analysis of variance) method and Regression method

- · Applied Genetic Algorithm, Evolutional Computation, and Fourier transformation to find better solutions
- Applied distributed computing to accelerate independent computation

Jan. 2019 - Jun. 2019

Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2020

Accelerating computation of Machine Learning by using Field-Programmable Gate Array

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- · Applied methods of SIMD(Single Instruction Multiple Data) with the low-level language of Verilog
- Reduced data size with SVD(Singular Value Decomposition)
- Rearranged units to utilize parallel computation

Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

Skills

Research and Development Stacks

Major Languages Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

Other Tools and Skills

Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Text Editors & IDE Vim, VSCode, Eclipse Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

VCS Git

Working Experience

SK Hynix Icheon, S.Korea

Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017 INTERN RESEARCHER

· Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures

• Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

Korean National Police Agency

Dokdo, S.Korea

DOKDO SECURITY POLICE Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

· Defended the disputed territory as a squad leader

Teaching Experience

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure , 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	Digital Computer Concept and Practice , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

Honors & Awards

Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACE

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

FULL SCHOLARSHIP